Guide to the Hervey Allen Papers, 1831-1965 SC.1952.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Published Material, 1919-1945; III.
  - Poetry, 1919-1935; 1.
    - Moments, in Contemporary Verse, April 1922 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Northern Earth Mood, in Poetry, March 1925 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - The Old Judge, in The Southern Review, September 1920 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Portentia, in The Reviewer, May 1922 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Refuge, in Contemporary Verse, October 1922 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Samples: Limited Edition Club, A Prefatory Essay, 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Saga of Leif the Lucky, in The Bookman, December 1923 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - The Sea-Islands, in Poetry, April 1922 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Southward Sidonian Hanno, in The Measure, October 1924 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Wampum and Old Gold, in The Yale Series of Younger Poets, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The Wanderer, in Contemporary Verse, June 1924 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - We, in Life, October 1919 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - When Shady Avenue Was Shady Lane, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Three Experimental Imprints, 1922 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Scope and Contents
      Privately printed book of poety including Black Roses, The Approach to Madness, and The Tree of Life in the Mystical Island. Published for Hervey Allen in Peterborough, NH. Back flap includes galley with edits.
  - Prose, 1926-1945; 2.
    This subseries includes Allen's personal copies and/or special editions of his published prose. Featured are individual short story and essay submissions to various publications. Some material is enclosed in special containers.
    - Action at Aquila: First Two Installments, in Cosmopolitan, October 1937; November 1937 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Blood Lust, in Cosmopolitan, July 1936 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Bread Loaf, in The Writer, April 1935 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Brief History: A Postscript, in Carnegie Magazine, October 1945 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - English and Choctaw, in The North American Review, June 1926 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - History and the Novel, in The Atlantic Bookshelf, and The Writer, February 1944; October 1944 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Jacob Sealy, An Epitaph, in The Bermudian, September 1932 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - A Personal Historian's Novel (Sanfelice Review), in The Saturday Review of Literature, June 1936 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Report to Major Roberts, in Cosmopolitan, February 1940 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Prose and Press About, 1920-1959; IV.
  This series consists of prose or press written about Hervey Allen and his work. It includes autobiographical and biographical notes, drafts, published material written by other authors, press coverage, newspaper clippings, obituaries and posthumous dedications about Hervey Allen and/or his work.
  - Autobiographical and Biographical Prose, 1933-1959; 1.
    This subseries details autobiographical and biographical material about Hervey Allen and/or his literary work. Included are press release statements from Farrar & Rinehart introducing Allen to the media; short essays written by other authors on Allen's work; manuscripts of term and theses projects on Allen and his work; and an unpublished manuscript entitled, "The Selected Poems of Hervey Allen" by Lawrence Lee. The manuscript names a foreword written by poet Robert Frost, however such foreword is not present in the manuscript.
    Also included in this material are some notes about the Allen family history.
    - Anthony Adverse and Mr. Allen, by William F. Allison in The Pittsburgh Record, November 1933 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Notes, Loose Leaf (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Notes, in The Pennsylvania Guardsman, August 1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Cow-boy (Hervey) Allen of Charleston, in The Literary Digest, August 1934 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Hervey Allen and His Poetry: A Biographical and Critical Sketch, by Alexander L. Blackburn, White Carbon Manuscript and Correspondence, May 1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Hervey Allen: A Modern Fennimore Cooper and Dr. Johnson by Ronald Williams, Typescript Manuscript and Notes (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - The Selected Poems of Hervey Allen with a Foreword by Robert Frost by Lawrence Lee, Typescript Manuscript (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Material (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
    - Bibliography Material (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - General Publicity and Press, 1920-1950; 2.
    In this subseries are newspaper clippings and general publicity statements about Allen and his work. Included are reviews, interviews, and itineraries of Allen's publicity tours.
    - Biographical, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Cartoons, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Personal and Prose, 1930-1948 (Box 40, Folder 13-15)
    - Poetry, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Clippings, 1924-1926 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, Press, and Reviews about Work, 1921-1950; 3.
    In this subseries are newspaper clippings, press releases, promotional posters, reviews, and publicity statements about particular Allen works.
    Oversized Material, Hervey Allen Promotional Posters, Box 192.
    - Action at Aquila, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Anthony Adverse, 1933-1936 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
    - The Disinherited Series, 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 4-6)
    - The Forest and the Fort, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Israfel, 1926-1949 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - It Was Like This: Two Stories of the Great War, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Toward the Flame, 1934-1950 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Toward the Morning, 1946-1948 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Toward the Morning, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Toward the Morning, 1948-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Wampum and Old Gold, 1921-1922 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Obituaries and Memorials, 1949-1953; 4.
    This subseries features newspaper clippings and press releases reporting on Hervey Allen's death. It also features documents relating to Allen's Arlington National Cemetery burial and memorials dedicated to Allen's memory at the University of Miami and University of Pittsburgh.
    - Obituaries, 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Arlington National Cemetery Grave, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - University of Miami Memorial, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Pitt Quarterly, 1948-1953 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence, 1903-1972; V.
  This series consists of general correspondence between Allen and individuals or institutions. While some correspondence with individual figures located in the General Correspondence may arguably be of literary nature, the material found in this series may include personal correspondence/subject matter, while the following Literary Correspondence series is thematically concentrated on literary production.
  - Individuals and Institutions, 1903-1972; 1.
    This subseries features Hervey Allen's general correspondence with individuals and institutions. Related correspondence can be found in other series (i.e. family correspondence and literary correspondence). This material may include business, personal, or philanthropic correspondence between Allen and other parties.
    An existing arrangement prior to the 2012 arrangement organized single loose correspondence material in alphabetical folders (i.e. Ta-Th), listed by surname or institution.
    - Abdullah, Achmed, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Ade, George, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Alexander, Elizabeth A., 1921-1947 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Aley, Maxwell, 1930-1949 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Alston, B. F., 1921-1922 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1938-1950 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - American Amateur Press Association, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - American Association of University Women, 1923-1948 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - American Battle Monuments Commission, 1926-1929 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1940-1949 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - American Committee for Refugee Scholars, Writers, and Artists, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - American Folklore Society, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - American Foundation, Inc., 1943-1947 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - American Friends of Lafayette, 1933-1934 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - American Legion, 1919-1945 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - American Library Association, 1933-1948 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - American Notes and Queries, 1941-1944 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - American Peoples Encyclopedia, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, E.H., 1921-1928 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Maxwell, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Appel, Doris, 1944-1949 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1929-1944 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Author's League of America, 1923-1948 (Box 45, Folder 23-24)
    - A-Al, 1921-1949 (Box 45, Folder 25-28)
    - Am-Ap, 1923-1949 (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
    - Ar-Az, 1918-1945 (Box 46, Folder 7-9)
    - Bacon, Leonard, 1926-1947 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
    - Baker, Charles, 1938-1949 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Baldwin, Jos. Honorable, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Bank of Manhattan Co., 1933-1943 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Barker, Mr. and Mrs. Virgil, 1934-1947 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Barr, Stringfellow, 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
    - Barrow, Elfrida, 1922-1923 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Barth, Sawyer Ramona, 1941-1949 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Barton, Alfred I, 1934-1941 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Bates, Francis, 1927-1928 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Bates, Katherine Lee, 1925-1926 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Baxter, John M., 1940-1949 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Beal, Howard, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Bedford Springs Hotel, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
    - Bellaman, Henry, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Benedict, C.M., 1921-1939 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1928-1943 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Benét, William Rose, 1923-1948 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Bennett, John, 1919-1949 (Box 47, Folder 11-14)
    - Bennett, Susan, 1921-1951 (Box 47, Folder 15-17)
      - April12-May 23, `1888
    - Bernays, Edward L., 1943-1945 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Bingham, Millicent, 1926-1933 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Biscaye Bay Yacht Club, 1946-1949 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Bobbs-Merrill Co., 1936-1948 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Bodenheim, Maxwell, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Bookman, The, 1921-1927 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Bradley Van Allen, 1948-1951 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Bragg, Laura M., 1925-1948 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Braithwaite, William Stanley, 1922-1926 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Brick Row Book Shop, 1922-1923 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Bromfield, Louis, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Broughton, Averall, 1930-1936 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Broughton, Phillip, 1944-1949 (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
    - Brown, Lawrence, 1933-1934 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Bushy Run Park, 1948-1949 (Box 48, Folder 10-11)
    - Butcher, Fanny, 1933-1948 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Bab-Bax, 1921-1949 (Box 48, Folder 13-16)
    - Bee-Beets, 1921-1948 (Box 48, Folder 17-20)
    - Bi-Bl, 1926-1949 (Box 48, Folder 21-23)
    - Bo-Boz, 1920-1948 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Br-By, 1919-1948 (Box 49, Folder 3-7)
    - Cambiare, C.P., 1935 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Canby, Henry Seidel, 1923-1941 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Carmer, Carl, 1940-1949 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1926-1948 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Chambrum, Jacques, 1939-1947 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Chapin, Henry, 1931-1949 (Box 49, Folder 13-16)
    - Churchill, Winston, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Coblentz, Stanton A., 1927 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Colum, Padraic, 1921-1935 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Conant, Isabel Fiske, 1924-1946 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Cook, Mrs. Anthony Wayne, 1921-1922 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Cram, Josephine B., 1925 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Crowell, Thomas Y., 1935 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Curtis Brown Ltd., 1935-1951 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Ca, 1922-1950 (Box 50, Folder 8-11)
    - Cha-Chu, 1927-1950 (Box 50, Folder 12-15)
    - Cla-Cly, 1935-1948 (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
    - Coa-Col, 1919-1950 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - Com-Con, 1928-1948 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
    - Coo-Cor, 1928-1950 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
    - Cos-Coy, 1928-1950 (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
    - Cr-Cz, 1920-1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Davidson, Edward, 1927-1949 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
    - Davidson, Natalie, 1927-1928 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Day, The John Co., 1931-1934 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - George H. Doran Co., 1923-1947 (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
    - Duell, Sloan and Pearce Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Dreppard, Carl W., 1943-1949 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Deutsch, Babbatte, 1922-1925 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - DeVoto, Bernard, 1937-1946 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Doubleday, Doran and Co., 1925-1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Doubleday, Page and Co., 1925-1944 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Douglas, Margory Stoneman, 1939-1949 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Dodd, Mead and Co., 1944 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Dodge, Howard A., 1935-1947 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
    - Drake, James F., 1921-1948 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Drinkwater, John, 1921-1923 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Dunbar Brander, AA, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Durham, Elizabeth Makolm, 1925-1926 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Dutton, E.P. and Co., Inc., 1937-1948 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Da-Di, 1928-1953 (Box 53, Folder 12-16)
    - Do-Dz, 1927-1949 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Edward MacDowell Association, 1927-1947 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
    - Eidesheim, Julie M., 1933-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Emery, Posey Byron, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1924-1935 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Engle, Paul, 1938-1949 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Erskine, John, 1922-1947 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Ea-Ek, 1924-1949 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - El-Ez, 1922-1949 (Box 55, Folder 8-12)
    - Farrar, Straus and Co. Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Franklin, Dwight, 1923-1934 (Box 55, Folder 14-15)
    - Frost, Robert, 1930-1948 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Frost, Susan Pringle, 1921-1927 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Fulton, John Dickson, 1916-1934 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Fa-Fe, 1923-1949 (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
    - Fi-Fl, 1923-1949 (Box 56, Folder 4-6)
    - Fo-Fu, 1922-1949 (Box 56, Folder 7-10)
    - Galt, Tom, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Gaul, Harriet, 1916-1950 (Box 56, Folder 12-14)
    - Gaul, Harvey, 1912-1948 (Box 56, Folder 15-17)
    - Gay, Robert, 1930-1939 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Goldsborough, T. Alan, 1936-1937 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Gow, J. Steele, 1920-1938 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Golloancz, Victor, Ltd., 1933-1941 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Grove, Robert, 1920-1940 (Box 57, Folder 5-6)
    - Ga, 1922-1949 (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
    - Ge-Go, 1903-1949 (Box 57, Folder 9-11)
    - Gr-Gz, 1922-1949 (Box 57, Folder 12-14)
    - Hatter and McNab, 1940-1949 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Harcourt, Brace and Co., 1920-1948 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1924-1949 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Harjes, C. Berwind, 1939-1946 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research, 1948-1949 (Box 58, Folder 5-6)
    - Henderson, Robert C., 1921-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Henniker-Heaton, Christopher Robin, 1940-1949 (Box 59, Folder 2-4)
    - Henniker-Heaton, Sir Herbert, 1927-1949 (Box 59, Folder 5-6)
    - Herald Tribune, 1933-1940 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Heyward, DuBose, 1921-1951 (Box 59, Folder 8-12)
    - Historical Association of Southern Florida, 1940-1949 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Hjort, Edith, 1947-1949 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Hodgson, E.F., Co., 1932-1939 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Holt, Henry and Co., 1939-1946 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1932-1939 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Howard, Sidney, 1919-1942 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Howland, William, 1940-1949 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Hufnal, Joseph M., 1932-1944 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Haa-Ham, 1920-1949 (Box 60, Folder 2-4)
    - Han-Haz, 1922-1950 (Box 60, Folder 5-7)
    - He-Hi, 1920-1949 (Box 60, Folder 8-9)
    - Hoa-Hoy, 1917-1962 (Box 60, Folder 10-12)
    - Hsieh, Chiao-Min, 1967-1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Hu-Hz, 1922-1954 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - In the Wake of the Ebb, From Marne to the Vesle (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - International Mark Twain Society, 1933-1949 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - I, 1921-1950 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Schuyler, 1922-1939 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Burgess, 1934-1948 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Johnston, Charles, 1934-1940 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - J, 1923-1950 (Box 61, Folder 9-12)
    - Keedrick, Lee, 1939-1948 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Ketchum, Carlton, 1921-1949 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Ketchum, Kenneth, 1926-1928 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Kinsolving, Sally Bruce, 1922-1939 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Kiskiminetas, Springs School, 1945-1948 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. Inc., 1933-1946 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Ka-Ke, 1919-1951 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - Ki-Kz, 1921-1949 (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1934-1948 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - Laing, Alexander, 1926-1951 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - League of American Writers, Inc., 1938-1940 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Lawrence, 1933 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Lewis, Mary (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Life Magazine, 1919-1939 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Limited Editions Club, 1934-1938 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Lindsey, Therese, 1921-1935 (Box 62, Folder 13-14)
    - Literary Guild for America, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Literary Review of the NY Evening Post, 1921-1924 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Little, Brown and Co., 1934-1945 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Longmans, Green and Co., 1935-1948 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Lowell, Amy, 1919-1946 (Box 62, Folder 19-20)
    - Lowes, John L., Prof., 1923-1944 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - La-Le, 1921-1949 (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
    - Li-Ll, 1920-1949 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Loa-Loy, 1920-1949 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
    - Lu-Lz, 1921-1949 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1920-1945 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - McCole, Camille, Prof., 1931-1935 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - McCormick, Samuel B., 1918-1930 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - MacDowell, 1921-1949 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - MacFarlane, George, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - The MacMillan Co., 1922-1949 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - McA-McD, 1920-1949 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
    - McE-McW, 1916-1949 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
    - Mabbott, Thomas Ollive, 1926-1941 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Maelstrom, 1944-1945 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Magazine, 1936-1953 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Mason, Scotty, 1937-1945 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - The Measure, 1921-1934 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Edward T., 1937-1947 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell, Margaret, 1940-1949 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Monroe, Harriet, 1921-1933 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Moore, Colleen, 1935 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Morrison, Theodore, Prof., 1930-1949 (Box 64, Folder 15-16)
    - Morrison, Mrs., 1950 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Ma-May, 1922-1949 (Box 65, Folder 1-7)
    - Me-Mi, 1922-1955 (Box 65, Folder 8-12)
    - Mo-Mos, 1921-1949 (Box 65, Folder 13-15)
    - Mot-Muy, 1920-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
    - Nash, Ogden, 1934-1936 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - National Institute of Arts & Letters, 1936-1950 (Box 66, Folder 5-10)
    - Naylor, Justus B., 1937-1948 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Naylor, Mrs., Lola B., 1927-1949 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Neff, Emery, 1925-1927 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - New Democracy, 1933-1936 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1926-1949 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - New York Hospital, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Newson, James C., 1934-1935 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - New York Times, 1923-1949 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - North American Review, 1919-1936 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Na-Nay, 1922-1949 (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
    - Ne-Noy, 1920-1949 (Box 67, Folder 8-10)
    - Nu-Nz, 1934-1939 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Owens, Hamilton, 1935-1950 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - O, 1916-1949 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
    - Patric, John, 1938-1949 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - The P.E.N. Club, 1925-1946 (Box 68, Folder 5-6)
    - Peppard, G.M., 1943-1949 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Peterboro Anthology, 1921-1923 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1921-1941 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1936-1947 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Phillips Academy, 1923-1931 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Pinckley, Josephine, 1921-1948 (Box 68, Folder 12-13)
    - The Players, 1927-1940 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Pleadwell, Frank Lester, 1927-1942 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Poetry, 1917-1949 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Porcher, Mary F. Wickham, 1924-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Porter, H.A., 1947-1948 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Pa-Pe, 1918-1949 (Box 69, Folder 3-5)
    - Phi-Por, 1921-1951 (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
    - Pos-Py, 1919-1950 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Q, 1921-1946 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1942-1949 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Random House, Inc., 1937-1944 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Ravenel, Beatrice, 1922-1927 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, 1919-1941 (Box 69, Folder 13-14)
    - Repp, Lida B., 1925-1943 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1938-1949 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, E.A., 1921-1935 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1940-1944 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Ross, Malcom, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Rudge, William Edwin, 1924-1936 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Russell, Ada, 1922-1933 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Ra-Re, 1918-1960 (Box 70, Folder 8-12)
    - Rh-Ru, 1921-1949 (Box 70, Folder 13-17)
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1924-1948 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
    - St. Gaudens, Paul, 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - St. John's College, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 4-7)
    - Schmitt, Howard, 1940-1946 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Scribner, Charles, 1934-1944 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Shady Side Academy, 1932-1949 (Box 71, Folder 10-11)
    - Sloane, William, 1939-1945 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Sloane, William Associates, 1940-1949 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Spicer-Simson, Theodore, 1921-1949 (Box 71, Folder 14-16)
    - The State, 1922-1925 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Strauss, Roger, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Surf Club Miami, 1934-1949 (Box 72, Folder 3-6)
    - Saa-Say, 1921-1949 (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
    - Sb-Sc, 1923-1951 (Box 72, Folder 9-11)
    - Sea-Sey, 1924-1949 (Box 72, Folder 12-13)
    - Sha-Shu, 1923-1949 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Si-Sm, 1918-1949 (Box 73, Folder 3-5)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1934-1935 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Sn-Sr, 1920-1950 (Box 73, Folder 7-10)
    - Sta-Sty, 1920-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
    - Su-Sy, 1922-1949 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Brice Odell, 1922-1923 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Katherine Garford, 1929-1948 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Thorpe, Francis N., 1916-1934 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Today's Woman, 1946 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Ta-Th, 1922-1949 (Box 74, Folder 9-11)
    - Ti-Tz, 1922-1951 (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
    - U, 1922-1949 (Box 76, Folder 1-3)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1925-1935 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Viking Press, 1933-1949 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Vinal, Harold, 1923-1927 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Voices; a Journal of Verse, 1922-1930 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - V, 1919-1952 (Box 76, Folder 8-10)
    - Wall, Berhnhardt, 1921-1925 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Waring, Tom R., 1921-1946 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Warner Brothers Studios, 1934-1938 (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
    - Wheeler, Elliot, 1938-1948 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Whitall, Ellen Stevens, 1922-1945 (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
    - Whittall, Mr. W. Van R, 1921-1945 (Box 78, Folder 4-6)
    - Wi-Wo, 1925-1949 (Box 78, Folder 7-9)
    - Widdemer, Margaret, 1932-1945 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Wilk, Jacob, 1935-1951 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Williman, Joan B., 1922-1923 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Ronald J., 1929-1949 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - The Writer, 1934-1947 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Wyeth, Andrew, 1943-1948 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Wylie, Philip, 1938-1947 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Wa-We, 1927-1951 (Box 79, Folder 6-11)